ranktactics.com 2016-10-30

# Our Privacy Policy | RankTactics.com

### _Ranktactics.com Privacy Policy (UPDATED 2/2014)_

### _Please Read The Following Privacy Policy Carefully Before Accessing Any Part Of The Website!_

### I. Overview

RankTactics recognizes and respects the privacy of users of RankTactics.com (the “Website”). The following privacy policy, as modified from time to time by us as described below (the “Policy”), tells you about the information that RankTactics collects through the Website and how we use the information we may collect. If you access the Website, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this Policy, as modified from time to time by us.

### II. Updates

RankTactics reserves the right to make changes to this Policy at any time, and will post any revised Policy on this page. You will know we have changed the Policy when you see a new updated date at the top of this Policy. RankTactics will not notify its Website users of any such changes by e-mail or other personal contact. We encourage you to check the date of this Policy whenever you visit this Website so that you will know when you need to review the Policy for modifications. Please note that this Policy applies to all information collected online by RankTactics.

### III. Collection & Use of Information

Personal information means information that can be used to identify and contact you, including but not limited to your name, postal delivery address, e-mail address, payment method (e.g., credit card or debit card) and telephone number, as well as other information when such information is combined with your personal information. When you register or use certain services available on our Website, we ask you to supply us with certain personal information so that we can provide, enhance and personalize our services and marketing efforts.

For similar reasons, we may supplement the personal information you provide with publicly available information about you. We use this personal information to process your registration, your payments, and to communicate with you on these and other topics. We may also use your e-mail address to send you newsletters, promotional announcements, and consumer surveys. Please note that you cannot unsubscribe from certain correspondence from us, including messages relating to your account transactions.

### IV. Viewing & Updating Your Information

You are responsible for updating and maintaining the truth and accuracy of the personal information you provide to us relating to your account. If you want to update your contact information, you should do so by visiting the Edit Profile section of our Website. You must be signed in to access the Edit Profile.

### V. Cookies & Other Technologies

As you browse the Website, cookies may placed on your computer’s hard drive. (Cookies are small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your hard drive for record keeping purposes.) In general, cookies can make the Web more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular site. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user’s computer. If your browser is set to not accept cookies, you may not be able to use particular services on the Website.

In addition to cookies, we may use other technologies, including pixel tags, to gather information on how our users interact with our Website and to otherwise help us efficiently operate and monitor our site and service. These technologies, show us, for example, popular pages, conversion rates, click-throughs and other information that can be used to improve, operate and monitor our site and our service.

### VI. Disclosure of Personal Information

We use other companies, agents or contractors to perform services on our behalf.  For example, we have partnered with other companies to personalize our Web pages, process credit card transactions, collect debts, analyze and enhance data, including customers’ interaction with our site, and process consumer surveys. In the course of providing such services, these other companies may have access to your personal information.  These companies are not permitted to use your personal information except for the purpose of providing the services we request of them.

In addition, we often partner with third party companies, agents or contractors in order to offer joint promotions, advertisements, programs and marketing campaigns in which we believe our users may be interested.  These companies are not permitted to use your personal information except for the purpose of participating in the partnership arrangement for which RankTactics engages them.

Moreover, by posting in the Deadbeat Complaint Center, you hereby consent to have your information disclosed to third parties in order to verify the complaint and facilitate any initiated Investigation Processes.

RankTactics also reserves the right to disclose personal information when we reasonably believe disclosure is required by law, if we reasonably believe disclosure is necessary to establish or exercise legal rights, or in situations involving potential threats to physical safety. In the event that RankTactics is acquired by or merged with a third party, we reserve the right, to sell or otherwise transfer the personal information we have collected as part of that transaction provided that such third party continues to honor our privacy policy.

NOTWITHSTANDING ANYTHING SET FORTH HEREIN TO THE CONTRARY, RANKTACTICS RESERVES THE RIGHT TO USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (EXCLUSIVE OF ANY CREDIT CARD INFORMATION PROVIDED, IF ANY) FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE, IN RANKTACTICS’S SOLE DISCRETION.  RankTactics may use your personal information to provide promotional offers to individuals by means of email advertising, text/short message services, telephone marketing, direct mail marketing, online banner advertising, and package stuffers, among other possible uses.

### VII. Security

You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account information and for restricting access to your computer or mobile device through which you access our Website account. Users of public or shared computers or unprotected mobile devices should log out at the completion of each visit to the Website.

Unfortunately, no security system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Accordingly, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information and cannot assume liability for improper access to it. By using this Website, or providing personal information to us through any means, you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of this site.

### VIII. Contact Information

If you have questions concerning your account, please contact Customer Service. If you have questions concerning this privacy policy, please email ranktacticscom@gmail.com

Our address is RankTactics: 57 Adastra Crescent, Markham, ON, L6C3C9
